answernest.com 2014-10-28

# Privacy Policy - AnswerNest

####  Privacy Overview 

Thank you for visiting [AnswerNest.com](htp://www.answernest.com) (the "Site"), an Answer Media (together with its affiliates, " Answer Media", "us," "our," or "we") website. Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used at the Site and in connection with the various services and software products we provide on or through the Site (collectively the "Services"). This Privacy Policy is hereby incorporated in our Terms of Service and by using the Site and Services, you accept the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not accept the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use any of the Sites or Services. 

####  Information Collected via the Website 

We collect Personally Identifiable Information ("PII") from the Site when you choose to provide it to us via an information request form, sign up or contact us email. PII is any information that can be used to identify or locate a particular person or entity. This includes, but is not limited to, name, postal address, telephone number or email address. Once collected, we will store your PII for Site usage purposes and promotional marketing efforts. 

We also collect Non-Personally Identifiable Information (Non-PII) via the Site and Services. Non-PII cannot be used to contact any single person or entity and may include, but is not limited to, IP address, content viewed, ad interaction, interaction with other advertiser websites, browser type, Internet Service Provider, the time/date of your visit to the website, your computer's operating system, search terms used and other click and browsing behavior. We use this information for internal purposes such as to improve and customize the Site and to understand and analyze how the Site is being used for marketing purposes. 

####  How We Track It: 

The Site and Services use either cookies and/or registry settings on your computer to store user information. A "cookie" is a small file containing a string of characters that is sent to your computer when you visit a website. Additionally, some ad networks may use web beacons in conjunction with cookies to compile aggregate statistics about usage on the Sites. A web beacon is a transparent image, typically in GIF format that can recognize certain types of information on a visitor's computer, such as a visitor's cookie number, time and date of page view, and a description of the page where the web beacon is placed. 

You may disable cookies on your web browser, thereby also rendering some web beacons unusable. You can use the Site and Services even if cookies are disabled, but this may impact our ability to adapt any of the Sites or Services according to your preferences. 

####  Public Forums 

The Site and Services, in some cases, allows for open forum-like communication via online forums, message boards, blog commentary and Q&A threads. Please note that any information disclosed in these areas may become public information. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your PII through these channels. 

####  Links and Third-Party Sites: 

This policy only addresses the Site and Services. Other websites, such as those to which we link or with which we co-brand or provide services via APIs or other extensibility may have their own policies. These other sites might independently collect data, solicit personal information, or send their own cookies to you. We are not responsible for any use of information when you use such third party sites. Additionally, in many cases, co-branded and API services that are jointly provided by us and selected companies will contain the sites' branding, but might not be hosted by us. In such cases, you should follow the privacy link on such site to determine which company's privacy policy protects the information you enter on such site. 

####  Information Sharing and Disclosure: 

In addition to using the anonymous identifying information that we track for internal purposes in the manner described, this information may also, on an aggregate basis, be shared with and used by third parties with which we have contracted (e.g., our third-party content providers and licensees of Answer Media' services). Furthermore, in addition to Answer Media providing its own advertising, Answer Media uses third-party advertising companies and networks to serve ads when you visit the Site. These companies and networks include, among others, third party ad servers, ad agencies, ad technology vendors, and research firms. These companies and networks may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to the Site in order to provide ads about goods and services of interest to you. In the course of serving advertisements to the Site, our ad networks may place or recognize a unique "cookie" on your browser or use a "web beacon." An example of such ad network is Yahoo, Inc. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by Yahoo, please refer to their advertising practices, terms and privacy. 

Certain third-party ad network providers may use web beacons and cookies to help present, better target, and measure the effectiveness of their advertisements, using non-personally identifiable data (such as sites visited and browser type) gathered over time and across their networks of Web pages to determine or predict the characteristics and preferences of their audience. This is also known as online behavioral advertising. 

Please note that ad networks' use of cookies or web beacons, and that of any other third-party that has a link available on any Site, is subject to their own privacy policies and not this privacy policy.   

####  Changes to This Privacy Statement: 

Answer Media may amend this policy from time to time by posting the new text on the Sites. Unless otherwise provided, the revised terms will take effect when they are posted. Once any changes that we make to this Privacy Policy become effective, your continued use of the Sites or Services after such time will signify your acceptance of the new terms. 

####  Questions or Suggestions: 

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding this privacy policy, please contact us. 

...
